Rise up!
Are you there?
In the name of Jesus Christ.
I'm preparing you to receive healing in the name of Jesus.
The SCOAN Sunday Service Prayer
I'm preparing you to receive deliverance in the name of Jesus.
To receive blessing in the name of Jesus.
Every dry bone, rise again.
Viewers at home, wherever you are, whatever you are doing right now, viewers -
you are here, we are there.
Begin to say: "Thank you, Jesus!" Say:
"Out of this body, you evil spirit, in the name of Jesus."
"Out of this life, you evil spirit, you demon, in the name of Jesus!"
The SCOAN Sunday Service Prayer
In the name of Jesus!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I command that devil in your temple, body - hands of sickness, disease and affliction,
you devil - say: "Out of this body!"
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Service Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Watch you screen, the kingdom of darkness is in disarray right now as people are manifesting.
The demons inside them right now are manifesting because of the fire of the Holy Spirit.
In the name of Jesus!
Do you know what it means?
If the devil is out of your body, disease, failure and setback are out of your life.
When we say 'out of this body', we mean, we separate everything that causes you pain, discomfort.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I say, out of this body! I say, out of this life!
You devil, you affliction, you disease, you setback.
Prayer!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Leave me alone. Yes, I'm the destroyer. Yes.
I'm destroying their life.
I'm finishing, yes, her children are suffering.
Yes, yes, I destroy them. I want to finish them.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
It is possible to separate your past from you.
Your past is failure, your past is affliction.
You believe that?
I command that devil, that affliction out of your body.
I say, out of your body, your blood, your kidney, your liver, your bone, your tendon.
I say, out of your body. I can't hear you.
Say: "Out of my body!" I can't hear you!
Say: "Out of my body, blood, you devil!"
Prayer!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You can see people still vomiting out strange substances from their system.
Poison they have eaten for so long on the table of the enemy. The Spirit of God Almighty
is flushing them out right now. So continue to pray.
She is my wife. Everybody hates her. Which career?
I say, everybody hates her - which career? She is my wife.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus, all knees shall bow!
I separate you from sickness, affliction; be separated.
I separate you from affliction, I separate you from disease. Your bone, be separated.
Your blood, be separated; your kidney, be separated; your liver, be separated.
I say, be separated. I can't hear you. Be separated!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
The Spirit of God is working within and outside you.
Right now, exploit it, get well, get delivered.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Watch your screen and see still people vomiting out the poisonous substances in their system -
strange substances, poisons they have eaten from the table of the enemy.
Right now the Spirit of the Living God is setting them free.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus.
Be healed.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Wherever that affliction, you are asked to leave, in the name of Jesus!
Leave, in the name of Jesus! Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
The right hand of God is power.
Begin to touch that affected part.
Wherever you have that pain, confess God's Word over your sickness and situation.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Watch your screen, see the strange substances.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I am a lion. We are many. I destroy him. I deported him back to Nigeria here.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Command them out!
You affliction, out!
Say: "Affliction, out!"
Prayer! Out! Say: "Out!"
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Be in an attitude of prayer.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
With all your heart, say: "Thank you, Jesus."
Confess your healing, confess your freedom.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Right now, begin to cover your way with the blood of Jesus.
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Ask for a new dawn, new dawn.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Your business, Good Morning!
Greet your career: "Good Morning!"
Greet your way: "Good Morning!" In the name of Jesus!
They are new every morning.
Good Morning, my career, future, finances!
Good Morning!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I cover you with the blood of Jesus.
I cover your way, career, life, family, direction, focus with the blood of Jesus.
In Jesus Christ's name!
Happy New Beginning!
Overflow Congregation
Right now, begin to walk in the new beginning - walk, talk and reason new.
Believe with all your heart.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I'm starting a new beginning!
Now, it is time to talk victory, think victory.
Old things passed away!
You have started it here.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Overflow Congregation
Tell your neighbour:
The Lord is your strength.
I have started today a new beginning.
The Lord is my strength.
Greet your neighbour.
The heart that believes will enjoy a new beginning.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
A new beginning is a victor.
The heart that believes - a new beginning.
Your heart believes? Rejoice.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
If God is your strength, it will happen.
It is not by your effort but it will happen.
It's by the grace of God, a new beginning.
You believe?
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Lord I believe
Help me overcome my unbelief
Everybody sing!
Lord I believe
Help me overcome my unbelief
Believing is the only condition for answered prayers
With my mouth I confess with my heart I believe
I believe God's Word is true for my life
Lord I believe
Help me overcome my unbelief
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You have overcome your unbelief.
Say: "I have overcome my unbelief."
So if you have overcome, the message is for you. The Word of God is true for your life.
So now you dance differently, look differently, smile differently, reason differently.
So your attitude nowadays is quite different because you have started a new beginning.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
The life you have started, God is your strength.
That is why you will not understand.
It's not your strength; you have ended your own strength and God's strength has started.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Your strength is past; God's strength is now.
Hallelujah!
How to maintain this strength - God's strength - the Word of God is the answer.
To maintain the blessing, the victory your have received - the Word of God.
The only way is the Word of God.
Meditate in it and the revelation will come, the strength will continue.
I'm seeing you maintaining God's strength.
I'm seeing you maintaining a new beginning.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Hallelujah! I'm rejoicing in your new beginning.
I'm rejoicing for you!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Every impossible becomes possible right now because of God's strength.
With God, all things are possible.
I'm prophesying to your life.
This is the Word of God for you. I'm seeing you maintaining your new beginning.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In your new beginning, defeat and failure are things of the past!
This is a decree. The new beginning you started today - defeat and failure are things of the past.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You can count how many defeats in the past -
and failure - are things of the past.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Rejoice!
Open your lips and give thanks to God. Give thanks to Him.
Prayer For The Nations With Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Your flag. Open your lips, pray for your nation.
God's intervention in my nation, in your nation.
And the nations that are not here, that are not represented - God's intervention. Prayer!
Prayer For The Nations With Prophet T.B. Joshua.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Ask God to intervene in the affair of your nation.
Calmness!
Calm and calmness take charge of the security of your nation.
Prayer For The Nations With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Economy of your nation - ask God to intervene.
Social and welfare of your nation - ask God to intervene.
God's intervention.
Prayer For The Nations With Prophet T.B. Joshua
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
TT: Monica Asefa
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 13/04/2019
TT Monica Asefa 11/04/19